marocbiz.info 2018-10-29

# privacy – marocbiz.info

This privacy policy applies to the information (the Site) collects about you from 

any device you use to access products, services, software, websites, and other goods 

and services offered, owned, or operated by (collectively “Services”). Some of these 

Services may provide you with additional information and choices about your privacy, 

which you should review.

This policy does not apply to information about you collected by third party 

websites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from the Site. The 

information collected or received by third parties is subject to their own privacy 

policies.

### Collection of Your Information

It is our policy to respect the privacy of the people who use the Services (each a 

“User,” collectively the “Users”). Therefore, we will not disclose to any 

unauthorized third party a User’s name or contact information. We will also not 

monitor, edit or disclose the contents of a User’s information unless required to do 

so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on 

us;

  * Protect and defend our rights or property;
  * Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Users 

or the public;

  * To prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk 

of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable; or

  * Fix or debug problems with our servers/software/service.

When you register to become a member of the Site and in the course of using the 

Site, you may voluntarily submit personally identifiable information that can be 

used to contact or identify you and administer your account (”Personal 

Information”). Personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, 

phone number and e-mail address. The Site may also collect Personal Information from 

you if you choose to opt-in to participate in sweepstakes, surveys, contests or 

competitions. When you register with the Site, you create your own profile and 

privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, e-mail and photo, 

are displayed to people you have specified in your privacy settings. Profile 

information you submit to the Site, and make public via your privacy settings, will 

also be available to other users via searching our Site, and may be available to 

third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and the 

content you create and store on the Site. We recommend that you guard your anonymity 

and sensitive information and that you not use your real name as your screen or user 

name to the extent that allows others to identify you.

As you use the Site, our servers automatically record information that the browser 

sends whenever it points to a Site or online service (”Log Data”). Log Data may 

include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser 

type, the web page you were visiting before you came to one of the Site and 

information you search for on a Site.

Your information may be supplemented with additional information from other 

companies such as publicly available information, information about households, and 

other information which we may append or match to your information.

The Site may also receive or collect certain technical information when you use our 

Services. This may include: your browser or operating system, your manner of 

connecting to the Internet (including the type of device you are using) and the name 

of your Internet service provider or wireless carrier; your Internet protocol (IP) 

address; information about Services that you used prior to registering with the 

Site; and data relating to malfunctions or problems occurring when you use the Site 

Services. Additionally, we may collect information about other software on your 

device for the limited purpose of protecting your security or improving your online 

experience.

### How Your Information is Used

Personal Information is used for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve 

our services, features and content; (ii) to administer your use of our services and 

your account; (iii) to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site; (iv) to 

better understand your needs and interests; (v) to fulfill requests you may make; 

(vi) to personalize your experience; (vii) to provide service announcements; and 

(viii) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties 

that we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing 

or promotional materials and other information on related services. If you decide at 

any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications, please follow the 

unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. Further, you may 

easily adjust your privacy and e-mail settings via your account settings at any 

time.

### Privacy Policy and Consumer Education

### Children’s Privacy

We do not direct the Site to persons under 13 years of age, and requires Users to be 

13 years or older. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect or maintain on the Site 

personally identifying or other information from persons under 13 years of age. If a 

parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal 

Information without their consent, he or she should contact info@, titled Privacy. 

If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, 

we will delete such information from our files.  
We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask a parent or guardian for permission 

before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### Consumer Education Related to Social Networking

Creating a safe social networking environment is important to us. While we do not 

target or knowingly allow users under 18 to use the Service, interested persons may 

visit the following links created by the Federal Trade Commission to learn more 

about social networking safety tips:

  * http://onguardonline·gοv/socialnetworking·html [[link](http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking.html)]
  * http://onguardonline·gοv/socialnetworking_youth·html [[link](http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking_youth.html)]

### Other Information/Logging and Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small 

data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. 

We use “persistent cookies” to save your username and login password for future 

logins to the Site. We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of our 

service, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor web 

traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Site. You can instruct your 

browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before 

accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, 

however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of 

the services.

We also use the services of a third-party advertising companies – such as Gοοgle 

Adsense – and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit 

the Site. These companies may use “non-identifying information” (which will not 

including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits 

to this Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and 

services of interest to you. Snippet from Gοοgle Adsense website :

> Google uses the DoubleClick cookie on publisher websites 
> 
> displaying AdSense for content ads. Subject to any applicable laws, rules and 
> 
> regulations, you will have the sole and exclusive right to use all data derived from 
> 
> your use of the DoubleClick cookie for any purpose related to your business, 
> 
> provided that Gοοgle may use and disclose this data subject to the terms of [Google’s advertising privacy policies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html "Google’s Advertising Privacy Policies") and any applicable 
> 
> laws, rules and regulations.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices 

about not having this information used by these companies, please visit Network 

Advertising Initiative (networkadvertising·org) and read their article regarding [Opt Out of Behavioral Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Opt Out of Behavioral Advertising").

### Information Sharing And Disclosure

_Members/Users._  
In addition to your username, any comments or submissions that you post to the Site 

will be publicly available. You post and share your Personal Information and content 

on the Site at your own risk. While we go to great lengths to create a safe and 

enjoyable experience on the Site, we cannot control the actions of other users with 

whom you may choose to share your content and/or profile information. In addition, 

we cannot anticipate other users’ ability to circumvent privacy settings. You 

understand that, even after removal of your Personal Information and content from 

the Site, copies of your information may remain viewable in cached or archived Web 

pages or on the local computers of users who may have downloaded or stored your 

information.  
Even with all the appropriate precautions we take to protect your information, we 

recommend you refrain from sending private information or Personal Information by 

e-mail, chat, or other messaging services.

_Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information._  
We may share aggregated information that includes non-identifying information and 

Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and to 

deliver targeted advertising about other products and services.

_Service Providers._  
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the our services, 

to provide the services on our behalf, to perform services related to administration 

of the Site (including, without limitation, maintenance, hosting and database 

management services, web analytics and administration). These third parties have 

access to your non-identifying personal information or log data (cookies) only to 

perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for 

any other purpose.

### Changing OR Deleting Your Information

All members/authors may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information 

in their registration profile by logging into their account and changing the “user 

preferences” associated with their account. If you completely delete all such 

information, your account may be deactivated. We may retain an archived copy of your 

records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### Our Commitment to Security

The Site concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ a variety of 

industry-standard measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized 

access.

The Site has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse 

of your information, but cannot guarantee that your information will never be 

disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a 

result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the Site 

and its affiliated providers’ policies). To protect your privacy and security, we 

may use passwords or other technologies to register or authenticate you and enable 

you to take advantage of the Services, and before granting access or making 

corrections to your information.

### International Transfer

Your “non-identifying” personal information may be transferred to – and maintained 

on – computers located outside of your state, province, country or other 

governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those 

in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the France and choose to provide 

information to us, please be advised that we transfer Personal Information to the 

France and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your 

submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Links To Other Sites

The Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by 

“clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third 

party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we 

link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an 

endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third 

party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or 

practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other 

websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data 

or solicit personal information from you. Other websites and services follow 

different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you 

submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the 

other websites you visit.

### Changes to this Privacy Notice and Additional Information

The Site may update this Privacy Notice from time to time, and so you should review 

this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to the Site’s information 

practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided 

other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from the 

Site as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that 

may be introduced in the future.

_Violations and Comments_  
Please report any violations of the TOS to abuse@, titled : Abuse/Violation; or make 

any comments to info@.

_Last Updated_  
Thursday, May 24th 2018 – 00:04:23 PM
